var quiz = [{"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Maintaining a registry of genetic material for the many varieties of an organism can be viewed as a form of sustainable agriculture based on a land ethic approach."}, {"answers": ["lumper", "Russet Burbank", "Peruvian", "New Leaf"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "In the early to mid-1800s, the Irish relied heavily on the production of _______ potatoes."}, {"answers": ["80", "35", "90", "50"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "____% of of all of the potatoes consumed are in fast food."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Trans fats are now illegal in the United States."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Despite the influence of culture and marketing, people always have a choice about what they eat."}, {"answers": ["Monocropping", "Marketing", "Branding", "McDonaldization"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "The term used for the process by which a single crop is grown and harvested to the exclusion of other types of crops is:"}, {"answers": ["Marketing", "Branding", "McDonaldization", "Food deserts"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "The term used for the rapid homogenization of food culture in the United States is called:"}, {"answers": ["Conservation", "Preservation", "Biotechnology", "Ecocentricism"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "To protect a potato from destruction for the use of humans is known as:"}, {"answers": ["Spatial fix", "McDonaldization", "Branding", "Monocropping"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "This is a marketing strategy centered on promoting a recognizable product through advertising exposure:"}, {"answers": ["imported", "GM", "frozen", "fresh"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "French fries make up 90% of the ___________ potato market."}, {"answers": ["Almost all crops are GM crops in one way or another.", "Not all farmers can afford the costly GM seeds.", "Humans are too trusting of these crops.", "Farmers are at a disadvantage since they must buy these patented seeds with each planting."], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "All of the following are problems associated with GM crops, EXCEPT:"}, {"answers": ["Irish farmers", "Peruvians", "Monsanto", "Nature"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "The \u201cNew Leaf\u201d potato was created by:"}, {"answers": ["environmental justice", "the spatial fix", "the second contradiction of capital", "the first contradiction of capital"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "The McDonaldization of the U.S. and the world is an example of _______."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "The U.S. fast food industry is largely responsible for the success of the Russet Burbank potato."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Lumper potatoes no longer exist."}, {"answers": ["hydrogenization", "monocropping", "domestication", "the land ethic"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following presents the greatest threat to agrodiversity?"}, {"answers": ["Hardees", "Burger King", "McDonalds", "Wendys"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Who is the largest buyer of potatoes in the world?"}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "The consumption of trans fat has always been known to be a health risk."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "By reducing the genetic diversity of potatoes we are setting ourselves up for another potato blight."}, {"answers": ["Risk", "Herbicides", "Labor", "Pesticides"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Which of the following is not a growth input for the Russet Burbank potato?"}, {"answers": ["neighborhoods with a low density of fast food restaurants", "neighborhoods with a low density of grocery stores", "low income neighborhoods", "neighborhoods with high rates of obesity and diabetes"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Food deserts are typically found in all of the following neighborhoods, EXCEPT:"}, {"answers": ["Genetically-maintained organisms", "Grossly-modified organisms", "Genetically-modified organisms", "Generically-modified organisms"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "GMOs are:"}, {"answers": ["underestimate; immediate", "overestimate; immediate", "overestimate; not immediate", "underestimate; not immediate"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "People are more likely to _______ the risks associated with trans fats because the consequences are _______."}, {"answers": ["True", "False"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "The Columbian exchange is the process by which Andean potatoes arrived in Europe."}, {"answers": ["Potatoes were originally viewed as food for the elite and wealthy.", "The Andeans were the first to domesticate the potato.", "Potatoes allowed the Irish to develop self-sufficiency.", "The Irish brought potatoes to North America."], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "Which of the following is NOT true regarding the history of the potato?"}, {"answers": ["It is the Peruvian national registry for potatoes", "Is a clear example of a preservation approach.", "Holds over 80% of the world\u2019s native potato and sweet potato cultivars", "Contains the genetic material for many varieties of potatoes"], "correctIndex": 1, "question": "Which of the following is NOT true regarding the CIP?"}, {"answers": ["Trans fats are present naturally in some foods", "The FDA is currently seeking to remove trans fats from the GRAS list", "Trans fats provide the mechanism to provide a smooth, creamy and well-mixed food", "in 1957 the AHA linked trans fats to heart disease"], "correctIndex": 3, "question": "All of the following are true statements about fats, EXCEPT:"}, {"answers": ["Biotechnology approach", "Preservation approach", "Anthropocentric approach", "Ecocentric approach"], "correctIndex": 2, "question": "Which approach would agree with the following statement, \u201cCreating new varieties of potatoes is a good thing as it will better serve the needs of humans\u201d:"}, {"answers": ["New Leaf", "Russet Burbank", "Lumper", "Peruvian"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "The production of _______ potatoes was discontinued because of consumer fears about pesticide ingestion."}, {"answers": ["Idaho", "Washington", "Michigan", "Utah"], "correctIndex": 0, "question": "The Russet Burbank is the major export of which state in the U.S.?"}]

quizCollection['16'] = quiz